<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"> <id>/</id><title>Andy</title><subtitle>A minimal, responsive, and powerful Jekyll theme for presenting professional writing.</subtitle> <updated>2022-07-24T19:57:00+00:00</updated> <author> <name>Andy</name> <uri>/</uri> </author><link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="/feed.xml"/><link rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" href="/"/> <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator> <rights> © 2022 Andy </rights> <icon>/assets/img/favicons/favicon.ico</icon> <logo>/assets/img/favicons/favicon-96x96.png</logo> <entry><title>In Search of the Lynwood Tunnel</title><link href="/posts/the-lynwood-tunnel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="In Search of the Lynwood Tunnel" /><published>2018-04-01T01:00:00+00:00</published> <updated>2022-07-24T19:54:38+00:00</updated> <id>/posts/the-lynwood-tunnel/</id> <content src="/posts/the-lynwood-tunnel/" /> <author> <name>andy</name> </author> <category term="Railways" /> <summary> I spent this Easter Sunday in Ardingly, and the previous night the discussion was focused around the proposed extension of the Bluebell Railway to utilise the disused link from Horsted Keynes to Haywards Heath. We were studying the local OS map, and didn’t see how the route would go through a set of houses on the Lindfield Road. All the aerial views suggested they were right in the way of the r... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Laura's Disco Hat</title><link href="/posts/lauras-disco-hat/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Laura's Disco Hat" /><published>2017-07-31T01:00:00+00:00</published> <updated>2022-07-24T19:54:38+00:00</updated> <id>/posts/lauras-disco-hat/</id> <content src="/posts/lauras-disco-hat/" /> <author> <name>andy</name> </author> <category term="Electronics" /> <summary> This past weekend Laura and I attended the wedding of Mike &amp;amp; Abi Bettle-Shaffer, and the guests were asked to attend in bright colours, bow-ties and hats/fascinators - there was even to be a competition for the best on in each category. Naturally bright colours + hats begged for some LEDs to be added to jazz things up! In order to save you the suspense, here is what we ended up with: The ... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>parkrun Around New Zealand</title><link href="/posts/parkrun-around-new-zealand/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="parkrun Around New Zealand" /><published>2016-01-09T01:00:00+00:00</published> <updated>2022-07-24T19:54:38+00:00</updated> <id>/posts/parkrun-around-new-zealand/</id> <content src="/posts/parkrun-around-new-zealand/" /> <author> <name>andy</name> </author> <category term="parkrun" /> <summary> Me on the Moeraki Boulders, Otago Coast, New Zealand I started parkrun in November 2014 after having been enticed along to the Fellfoot parkrun by my friend Anna whilst visiting up in Kendal. It was in inauspicious start as I had no suitable shoes, nor shorts, so I borrowed some kit to run my first ever 5k. Surprisingly I managed the course in 26:19, and after that I was hooked. A year later... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Cycling The South Downs Way</title><link href="/posts/cycling-the-south-downs-way/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cycling The South Downs Way" /><published>2015-08-31T01:00:00+00:00</published> <updated>2022-07-24T19:54:38+00:00</updated> <id>/posts/cycling-the-south-downs-way/</id> <content src="/posts/cycling-the-south-downs-way/" /> <author> <name>andy</name> </author> <category term="Cycling" /> <summary> Cycling the South Downs Way: Winchester to Eastbourne Towards the end of last year I set myself a target, I wanted to complete my personal ‘big three’ cycle rides in a calendar year, one of which I had never done before… Ride 1: May 2015, The Isle of Wight Randonee. A nice introduction to the year with the annual Isle of Wight ride, organised by the Wayfarer CTC each year on the Sunday of th... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>LED Disco Bike</title><link href="/posts/led-disco-bike/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="LED Disco Bike" /><published>2015-08-23T01:00:00+00:00</published> <updated>2022-07-24T19:56:32+00:00</updated> <id>/posts/led-disco-bike/</id> <content src="/posts/led-disco-bike/" /> <author> <name>andy</name> </author> <category term="Cycling" /> <category term="Electronics" /> <summary> This year I decided to ride the Dunwich Dynamo, having done it once before in 2012. For those of you not in the know, it is a 186km ride from London Fields in Hackney, out to the Suffolk coastal town/village of Dunwich, done (mostly) overnight. It’s a relaxed, friendly affair - definitely not a race, and the light-hearted nature of the event attracts a wide range of people and bikes. Included i... </summary> </entry> </feed>
